printaholic.com 2015-12-06

# Privacy Policy - Printaholic.com | Printaholic.com

At Printaholic.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by Printaholic.com and how it is used. If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us here.  
Log Files

Like many other Web sites, Printaholic.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.  
Cookies and Web Beacons

Printaholic.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.  
DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Printaholic.com.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to Printaholic.com and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Printaholic.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Printaholic.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Printaholic.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.  
Right to Opt Out

Printaholic.com gives users the opportunity to opt-out of having their information used for purposes not directly related to the site at the point where we ask for the information, including the sharing of personal information with third parties for their own marketing purposes. Please be aware that this may result in our not being able to provide certain services to you that require us to share information with third parties. If you choose to receive communications from us but later wish to discontinue receiving communications or our services, you can opt-out by contacting us via email or mail using the contact information provided below.

All email correspondence from Printaholic.com are fully CAN-SPAM compliant and will contain clear instructions for opting out of all email communications. Please note that opting out of receipt of promotional e-mail communications will only affect future activities or communications from us. If we have already provided your information to a third party before you have changed your preferences or updated your information, you will have to change your preferences directly with that third party. To opt-out of communications from our third party business partners, please contact them directly.

Update

This Privacy Policy was last updated on: Monday, October 12, 2012.

Printaholic.com  
c/o Digital Brands Inc.  
15 SE 1st Ave, Suite B  
Gainesville, FL 32601  
contact@Printaholic.com
